

Ramadhan Gamasmara



Khusaeri St. 39th, Trikora Complex, Halim P. East Jakarta



rgamasmara@gmail.com



+62 877 - 8153 - 9476

SOCIAL



Ramadhan Gamasmara



@gamski1



gamasmara

EDUCATION

 Bachelor of Computer Information Systems

GPA: 3.37

Bina Nusantara University

2016 - 2020

Formal Education

42 SHS Jakarta

2013 - 2016

Formal Education
80 JHS Jakarta

2010 - 2013

HOBBIES











PROFILE

An Information System graduate with past working experiences of doing tasks revolving Web App Development, Quality Assurance, Data and Fraud Analytics. I am always open to new opportunities, enthusiastic to learn new things, and always ready to undertake new challenges in the future.

EXPERIENCES

PT Mastersystem Infotama

Feb 2019 - Feb 2020 Knowledge Management Intern

Was placed in a Knowledge Management System Web App Development Team, and was given responsibility to handle tasks that includes creating Company's Knowledge Article Posts based on past Projects, took part in App Development activities, helped doing QA Functional Testing, create documentations, helped in data organizing tasks like cleaning data, querying data from database, filtering data, make a visualization out of it, and make reports.

Shopee Indonesia

Sept 2021 - Oct 2022 Fraud Analyst

As a Fraud Analyst at Shopee Indonesia, my job was to analyze thousands of customer logged data and activities in order to investigate anomalies that can lead to many ways or methods of fraudulent and abusive act performed by users/customers. Users/Customers that are caught doing a fraudulent and abusive act will be given punishment based on the current running SOPs.

From the daily fraud analysis, finding out and learning new ways of fraudulent and abusive methods and loopholes, and figuring out patterns used by fraudsters and abuser was also our high priority task.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- Power BI
- Adobe Photoshop

- CSS3
- MS. Office
- Adobe Illustrator

- JavaScript
- Sony Vegas Pro
- MySQL
- Adobe Premiere

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Positive Attitude
- Communication
- Listening
- Problem Solving
- Empathy

LANGUAGES

- Indonesian
- English